Baby Bear, Baby Bear Please don't cry.
Baby Bear, Baby Bear Come on our picnic!
Do you like chicken? No, I don't.
Do you like ham? No, I don't.
I want something sweet to eat!
Baby Bear, Baby Bear Please don't cry.
Baby Bear, Baby Bear Come on our picnic!
Do you like cheese? No, I don't.
Do you like yoghurt? No, I don't.
I want something sweet to eat!
Baby Bear, Baby Bear Please don't cry.
Baby Bear, Baby Bear Come on our picnic!
Do you like carrots? No, I don't.
Do you like tomatoes? No, I don't.
I want something sweet to eat!
Baby Bear, Baby Bear Please don't cry.
Baby Bear, Baby Bear Come on our picnic!
Baby Bear, Baby Bear Here's some honey
It's sweet and delicious
Yummy, yummy, yummy!