Mummy, daddy, sister, brother and me.
This is my wonderful family!
This is my mummy. Surprise, surprise!
She's got fair hair and she's got blue eyes.
Mummy, daddy, sister, brother and me.
This is my wonderful family!
This is my daddy. Surprise, surprise!
He's got black hair and he's got brown eyes.
Mummy, daddy, sister, brother and me.
This is my wonderful family!
This is my sister. Surprise, surprise!
She's got fair hair and she's got brown eyes.
Mummy, daddy, sister, brother and me.
This is my wonderful family!
This is my brother. Surprise, surprise!
He's got black hair and he's got blue eyes.
Mummy, daddy, sister, brother and me.
This is my wonderful family!