Five little rabbits go out to play and hunt for eggs on Easter day.
One little rabbit finds a big red egg.
Eats it all and runs away.
Four little rabbits go out to play and hunt for eggs on Easter day.
One little rabbit finds a big yellow egg.
Eats it all and runs away.
Three little rabbits go out to play and hunt for eggs on Easter day.
One little rabbit finds a big blue egg.
Eats it all and runs away.
Two little rabbits go out to play and hunt for eggs on Easter day.
One little rabbit finds a big green egg.
Eats it all and runs away.
One little rabbit goes out to play and hunts for eggs on Easter day.
One little rabbit finds a big pink egg.
Eats it all and runs away.